Prakashbhai Koli

Computer Science

Experienced IT Specialist with a good background in designing and developing. 1+ years of industry experience. Excellent problem solving skills and ability to perform well in a team. Seeking to help company, as well as grow and develop my own skills.

koliprakashbhai555@gmail.com

Pune, India

prakashbhai555.github.io/pkportfolio/

+91- 79723-94788

iii 05 May, 1995

in linkedin.com/in/prakashbhai-koli-99711819b

WORK EXPERIENCE

jr. Software Developer (Intern)

Hands in Technology

01/2020 - 07/2020 Kandivali, Mumbai

handsintechnology.com

Tasks

 As Intern was working on Magento2 PHP Framework for updating, solve some config. file bugs, as well as manually Testing some Live Projects on Android, iOS, and web App.

Associate Software Engineer

Vistaar Digital Media Pvt. Ltd.

07/2021 - 03/2022 Boriwali, Mumbai

www.vistaardigital.com

Tasks

 As Software Engineer experienced on developing web application and work on Emailers, Edetailing, Git, SQL, JS, Drupal, WordPress, WIX

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Application

R.C Patel Institute Of Management Research And Development, Shirpur

08/2017 - 04/2020 NMU, Jalgaon

- Computer Science

64.00 %

Bachelor of Computer Science

S.P.D.M College, Shirpur

07/2014 - 01/2017 NMU, Jalgaon 62.00 %

- Computer Science

HSC

New High School, Taloda

07/2011 - 05/2012 Nashik Board

51.33

- Science Stream

SSC

K.P.Patil School, Bhaler

07/2009 - 05/2010 Nashik Board

74.60

Marathi Medium

SKILLS

Team Work

Multitask

Helpful

Energetic

TECHNICAL SKILL

SQL, PL/SQL, C++

HTML, CSS, PHP

Emailers, Edetailing, Git

Magento2, WordPress, WIX, Figma

COLLEGE PROJECTS

One Stop NRI Advisory. (Smart Mobile Application)

 In the project Admin can provide the packages and subservices for user to order as per there requirements. The need of this project is Windows platform, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, JS, etc.

CERTIFICATES

Introduction to WordPress 🗗

Front end Development - HTML

MY WORK/OTHERS LINKS

Dribbble (UI/UX Designing Portfolio)

Online Shopping (Made with Google Site for shopping)

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS/HOBBIES

Puzzle Solving

Photography

Travelling